System Dynamic Society; Records ua435
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Conferences, 1976-2018
  - Athens, Greece, 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
    - Papers, 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Sedehi, Habib with Edoardo Mollona, Stefano Armenia and Roberto Berchi, "Comparing different approaches in teaching System Dynamics in Italian Universities", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Sedehi, Habib, "SYstem Dynamics Italian Chapter (SYDIC) Special Poster Presentation", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Skraba, Andrej with Crtomir Rozman, Miroljub Kljajic, Karmen Pazek, Martina Bavec, Franc Bavec and Davorin Kofjac, "Strategy for organic farming model development", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Slinger, Jill with Pål Davidsen, "Special Interest Group on Model Analysis (SIG-MA) Poster Presentation", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Slinger, Jill with Jan Kwakkel, "Does learning to reflect make better modellers?", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Sliskovic, Merica with Ante Munitic and Gorana Jelic Mrcelic, "Influence of variable catch factors on sardine population level in eastern Adriatic tested by System Dynamics", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Soto-Torres, M. Dolores with Ramon Fernandez-Lechon and Pedro Fernandez Soto, "The influence of subsidies on economic development: a system dynamics model", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Soyler, Hasan with Yusuf Cukaci, Ibrahim Aksu and Zahide Nesrin Omac, "Socio-Economic Development Projection Of Malatya Supported By EU Regional Development Programme: A System Dynamics Approach", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Stamboulis, Yeoryios with Yeoryios Kalaouzis, "Strategic Dynamics of the Project Based Organization", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Stamboulis, Yeoryios with George Papachristos, "Investigation and modelling framework of biofuels as a new socio-technical regime", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Stamboulis, Yeoryios, "Exploring the System Dynamics of Innovation Systems", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Stave, Krystyna, "Zero Waste by 2030: A system dynamics simulation tool for stakeholder involvement in Los Angeles' solid waste planning", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Sun, Amy with Vincent Tidwell, Geoff Klise, Leonard Malczynski, Will Peplinski and Jim Brainard, "System Dynamics Model of Southwestern New Mexico Hydrology to Assess Impact of the 2004 Arizona Water Settlements Act", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Sveen, Finn Olav with Jose Mari Sarriegi and Jose Gonzalez, "The Access Problem", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Svensson, Mats with Yengoh Genesis Tambang, "Low External Input Strategies for Sustainable Small-Scale Farming in Kenya - A Systems Dynamic Approach", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Tako, Antuela with Stewart Robinson, "Model building in System Dynamics and Discrete-event Simulation: a quantitative comparison (Dana Meadows Award Winner)", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Tawileh, Anas with Stephen McIntosh and Haya Al Magwashi, "A Systems Dynamics Approach to Assessing Policies to Tackle Alcohol Misuse", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Taylor, Ivan with Luminita Stemate, Guillaume Gagne and Anissa Frini, "Investigating the Effectiveness of Various Crowd Confrontation Strategies Using Vensim and the Phoenix Integration Suite", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Thun, Jörn-Henrik, "The Diffusion of System Dynamics analyzed with System Dynamics - A Diffusion Model Considering Network Externalities", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Triantis, Kostas with Warren Vaneman and Kalyan Pasupathy, "Dynamic Performance Measurement and Evaluation: Will Bridging Paradigms Lead to Improved System Design?", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Turkgulu, Burak, "Collapse of Easter Island:A Study to Understand the Story of a Collapsing Society", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Ulli-Beer, Silvia with Mathias Bosshardt, Fritz Gassmann and Alexander Wokaun, "Citizens' Choice: Modeling long term technology transition in the automobile industry", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Vaishnav, Chintan, "Does Technology Disruption Always Mean Industry Disruption?", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Vakili, Keyvan with Mohammad Isaai and Arash Jalali Barsari, "Strategic Assessment of Transportation Demand Management Policies: Tehran Case Study", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Vickland, Victor with Geoff McDonnell, "When accuracy matters: Prevalence, incidence and mortality rate in an Agent Based model of dementia management", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Vo, Thi Le Hoa with Daniel Thiel, "A System Dynamics Model of the Chicken Meat Supply Chain faced with Bird Flu", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Wansart, Joerg with Grit Walther and Thomas Spengler, "Limiting motor vehicles' CO2 emissions - a manufacturer's challenge", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Warren, Kim with Christina Spencer, "Workshop - Teaching Strategy Dynamics", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Whitmore, Andrew with Eliot Rich and Mark Nelson, "Building on Shifting Sands: The Structure of Repetitive IT Project Escalation, Crisis, and De-escalation", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Wolstenholme, Eric with Douglas McKelvie, David Monk, David Todd and Carol Brady, "Emerging Opportunities for System Dynamics in UK Health and Social care- The Market-Pull for Systemic Thinking", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Yamaguchi, Kaoru, "Open Macroeconomies as A Closed Economic System - SD Macroeconomic Modeling Completed -", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Yap, Yin, "Assessing The Level Of Unity And Integration In Malaysia Using The System Dynamics Simulation Model", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Yucel, Gönenç with Cornelia van Daalen, "When does it really make a difference? Experimenting with the actor-heterogeneity in modeling socio-technical transitions", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
      - Zimmermann, Nicole, "Implementing Electronic Trading at the New York Stock Exchange: A Case of Organizational Change", 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
    - Conference Photos, 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
    - Sponsors, 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
    - Sponsor Notes, 2008 July 20-2008 July 24
  - Boston, MA, USA, 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
    - Conference Website, 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
    - Call for Papers, 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
    - Sessions by Thread, 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
    - Abstract Proceedings, 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
    - Papers, 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Adamides, Emmanuel with Nikolaos Pomonis and George Papachristos, "Path dependence and transients in random and adaptive walks on strategy fitness landscapes", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Akkermans, Henk with Willem van Oppen, "From Mopping the Floor to Fixing the Plumbing: How KPN Telecom Uses SD to Improve Ramp-ups In its Service Supply Network", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Akkermans, Henk, "Beyond Rounding Up the Usual Suspects: Towards Effective Quality Management Policies for Production Ramp-ups in Supply Chains", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Altamirano, Mónica with Juha Aijo and Pertti Virtala, "A Qualitative Analysis of Periodic Maintenance of Roads", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - An, Lianjun with Young Lee, "Modeling Dynamics of Workforce Absenteeism and Effectiveness of Mitigation Actions During Pandemics", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Andersen, David with George Richardson, Fran Ackermann and Colin Eden, "Two Group Model Building Scripts that Integrate Systems Thinking into Strategy Workshops Facilitated with Group Explore", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Andersen, David with John Morecroft and Roberta Spencer, "How the System Dynamics Society Came to Be: A Collective Memoir", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Anderson, Edward with Laura Black, "Accumulations of Legitimacy: Exploring Insurgency and Counter-Insurgency Dynamics", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Arango, Santiago with Erling Moxnes, "Cyclical behaviour in electricity markets: an experimental study", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Araujo, Ewandro with Luc Cassivi, Martin Cloutier and Elie Elia, "Improving the Software Development Process: A Dynamic Model Using the Capacity Maturity Model", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Arndt, Holger, "Using System Dynamics-based Learning Environments to Enhance System Thinking", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Arquitt, Steven, "The dynamics of nutrient reduction trading: a simulation-based search for effective poicy design", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Askar, Mohamed with Ahmed Marzouk and Maha Resk, "Modeling the Dynamics of the Egyptian Stock Market", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Atilgan, Canan with Güven Demirel and Ali Rana Atilgan, "Landscape Dynamics of El Farol attendees", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Azar, Ahmad with Khaled Wahba and Abdalla Mohamed, "System Dynamics Highlights the Effect of Maintenance on Hemodialysis Performance", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Barlas, Yaman with Birnur Ozbas and Onur Ozgun, "Modeling of Real Estate Price Oscillations in Istanbul", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Bassi, Andrea, "Threshold 21 (T21) USA: Behavior Description", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Bayer, Steffen with Martina Koberle-Gaiser and James Barlow, "Planning for Adaptability in Healthcare Infrastructure", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Beall, Allyson with Andrew Ford, "Participatory Modeling for Adaptive Management: Reports from the Field II", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - BenDor, Todd, "Modeling the Wetland Mitigation Process: A New Dynamic Vision of No Net Loss Policy", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Bier, Asmeret with Andrew Ford, "A Classroom Simulation of a Tradable Green Certificate Market and Implications for Model Development", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Bivona, Enzo with Francesco Ceresia and Giovan Battista Montemaggiore, "Exploring the Underground Economy through System Dynamics to support Public Decision Makers: a preliminary qualitative analysis", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Bivona, Enzo, "Exploring Intellectual Capital Investments Policies in a Call Center through A 'System Dynamics' Resource Based View", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Bosshardt, Mathias with Silvia Ulli-Beer, Fritz Gassmann and Alexander Wokaun, "Developing a diffusion model of competing alternative drive-train technologies (cadt-model)", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Brady, Malcolm, "Advertising effectiveness and spillover: simulating strategic interaction using advertising", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Braun, Bill, "The Dynamics of the Eroding Goals Archetype", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Buendia, Fernando, "Self-organizing Markets", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Bueno, Newton, "A macroeconomic systemic model for the Brazilian economy", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Burns, James with Balaji Janamanchi, "Dynamics of a Democracy Deeply in Debt: Simulation Studies of Federal Revenue and the Capacity of the U.S. to Service its Debt", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Butler, John with Wai-ming Mak, "Organizational Growth and Population Dynamics: Strategies for Success", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Cavana, Robert with Martin Tobias, "Using system dynamics to analyse policy options for tobacco control in New Zealand", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Chaim, Ricardo, "Dynamic Stochasticity in the control of liquidity in Asset and Liability Management (ALM) for pension funds", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Chang, Myong-Hun, "Non-Equilibrium Industry Dynamics with Knowledge-Based Competition: An Agent-Based Computational Model", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Chichakly, Karim, "Modeling Agile Development: When is it Effective?", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Chichakly, Karim, "SMILE and XMILE: A Common Language and Interchange Format for System Dynamics", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Chiong Meza, Catherine with G.P.J. Dijkema and Cornelia van Daalen, "Scenario Analysis using System Dynamics Modelling:The case of Production Portfolio Change in the Dutch Paper and Board Industry", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Chirico, Francesco with Gianluca Colombo, "The effect of Family Inertia on the Value Creation Process in Family Firms: New Insights from a Simulation Study", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Chomiakow, Daniel, "A Generic Pattern for Modeling Manufacturing Companies", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Choucri, Nazli with Daniel Goldsmith, Stuart Madnick, J. Bradley Morrison and Michael Siegel, "Using System Dynamics to Model and Better Understand State Stability", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Clark, Thomas with Mary Jones, "Achieving Competitive Advantage in a High Turnover, Dynamic Market: A Causal Model Approach", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Cody, John with Robert Cavana and David Pearson, "Social structure and health: preliminary work on a system dynamics 'concept model'", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Comaschi, Carlo with Vincenzo Di Giulio and Eleonora Sormani, "Natural gas demand and supply in Italy", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Cooke, David with Huiming Yang, Gil Curry, Paul Rogers, Thomas Rohleder, Robert Lee and David Strong, "Introducing System Dynamics Modeling to Health Care in Alberta", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Cronrath, Eva-Maria with Alexander Zock, "Forecasting the Diffusion of Innovations by Analogies: Examples of the Mobile Telecommunication Market", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Cruz Barrientos, Margarita, "Evaluating System Dynamics as a Tool for Teaching History (Barry Richmond Award Winner)", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Dattee, Brice with David FitzPatrick, Henry Weil and Steffen Bayer, "The Dynamics of Technological Substitutions", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Deegan, Michael, "Exploring U.S. Flood Mitigation Policies: A Feedback View of System Behavior", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Du, Yong, "Incorporating System Dynamics Modeling into Goal-oriented Adaptive Requirements Engineering", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Dudley, Richard, "The Equity Supply Chain: Is it the Cause of So Few Women in Management and Leadership Positions?", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Duggan, Jim, "A Simulator for Continuous Agent-Based Modelling", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Dulac, Nicolas with Brandon Owens, Nancy Leveson and John Carroll, "A Hybrid Approach to the Creation of Dynamic Risk Management Models", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Duran Encalada, Jorge with Alberto Paucar-Caceres, "Sustainability Model for the Valsequillo Lake in Puebla, Mexico: Combining System Dynamics and Sustainable Urban Development", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Dutt, Varun with Cleotilde Gonzalez, "Slope of Inflow Impacts Dynamic Decision Making", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Dyner, Isaac with Santiago Arango and Carlos Franco, "Can a Reliability Charge Secure Electricity Supply? An SD-based assessment of the Colombian power market", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Egner, Joanne with Karim Chichakly and Paul Gisborne, "Getting Started with STELLA and iThink", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Ellison, James with Andjelka Kelic and Thomas Corbet, "Is A Natural Gas Strategic Reserve for the US Necessary? A System Dynamics-Based Approach", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Eskici, Burak with Burak Turkgulu, "Modeling the Dynamics of Avian Influenza Epidemics and Possible Pandemics (Best Poster Award Winner)", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Ewers, Mary with Lori Dauelsberg, "Pandemic Influenza Mitigation Strategies and their Economic Impacts", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Fincher, Stephanie with Krystyna Stave, "A Proactive Approach for Particulate Matter Air Pollution Management", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Ford, Andrew, "Global Warming and System Dynamics", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Forest, Tom, "Maya Apocalypse: Warfare-Punctuated Equilibrium at the Limit of Growth", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Forrester, Jay, "System Dynamics—the Next Fifty Years", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Fracassi, Eduardo, "Workshop - The Career Simulator - Which ar the key decisions in Career Planning?", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Franck, Travis, "Choice of utility functions in integrated assessment: how subjective well-being can influence policy analysis", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Franco, Douglas, "Fifty Years of Table Functions", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Friedman, Sheldon with Steven Cavaleri and Mike Raphael, "Individual Learning Style and Systems Tool Preferences", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Fryling, Margaret, "The Dynamics of ERP Success", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Garagic, Denis with Iavor Trifonov, Paolo Gaudiano and David Dickason, "Agent-Based Modeling as a Tool for Manpower and Personnel Management", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Garcia, Rosanna, "Co-opetition for the Diffusion of Resistant Innovations: A Case Study in the Global Wine Industry using an Agent-based Model", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Gary, Shayne with Martin Kunc, John Morecroft and Scott Rockart, "System Dynamics and Strategy: Accomplishments and Future Opportunities", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Gary, Shayne with Robert Wood, "Testing the Effects of a System Dynamics Decision Aid on Mental Model Accuracy and Performance on Dynamic Decision Making Tasks", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Garzia, Carmine, "Untangling the Origins of Strategic Innovation. A System Dynamics Approach", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Gassmann, Fritz with Mathias Bosshardt, "Theory of Stable Dynamical Systems", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Ghaffarzadegan, Navid with Amir Tajrishi and Niyousha Hosseinichimeh, "Economic Transition Management in Iranian Cement Industry", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Ghaffarzadegan, Navid, "How a System Backfires: From a Redundancy Solution to Redundancy Problems in Security", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Goncalves, Paulo, "Returns in the Corn Supply Chain", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Groesser, Stefan with Matteo Pedercini, "Student Chapter Poster Presentation", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Groesser, Stefan, "The Structure and Dynamics of the Residential Building: Which Mechanisms Determine the Development of the Building Stock?", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Groesser, Stefan with Suzanne Bruppacher, "Decisions in the Construction Process of the Residential Building Environment: Development of a Static and Dynamic Model", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Groessler, Andreas with Peter Milling, "Inductive and Deductive System Dynamics Modeling", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Groessler, Andreas with Alexander Zock, "Tell me 'why' or 'how' – A Heuristic to Choose between Quantitative and Qualitative Systems Analysis", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Haslett, Tim, "From Hospital Plans to Computer Simulation: A Case Study of the Alfred Centre.", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Heijkoop, Gerrit with Scott Cunningham, "System Dynamics Modeling of Benefit Realization When Adopting New Software", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Helal, Magdy with Luis Rabelo, Jose Sepulveda and Albert Jones, "A methodology for Integrating and Synchronizing the System Dynamics and Discrete Event Simulation Paradigms", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Ho, Yufeng, "Simulation and Analysis of Taichung Urban Ecosystem", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Homer, Jack with Gary Hirsch and Bobby Milstein, "Chronic Illness in a Complex Health Economy: The Perils and Promises of Downstream and Upstream Reforms", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Hovmand, Peter with David Ford, Stavroula Kyriakakis and Ingrid Flom, "Women Arrested for Domestic Violence: Unintended Consequences of Pro and Mandatory Arrest Policies", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Hovmand, Peter with David Gillespie, "Dynamics of Innovation Implementation and Organizational Performance in Mental Health Services", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Howick, Susan with Jason Whalley, "Broadband adoption: the case of rural and remote Scotland", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Hu, Qian, "An experimental study on the construction of electricity power stations in China", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Huang, Lizhen, "The bullwhip effect in the closed loop supply chain", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Incioglu, Firat, "A Dynamic Simulation Model for Long-Term Hypertension Progression", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Jay, Jason with George Roth, "From Continuous Improvement to Centralized Information: The Life and Times of a Systems Thinking Intervention", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Jia, Jianguo with Yu Lu, "System Dynamics Modeling for Overtime Management Strategy of Software Project", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Jia, Jianguo with Jianxun Chu and Yu Lu, "System Dynamics Modeling for Medicine Price Policy in China", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Jia, Renan with Cuixia Wang and Xiaojing Jia, "A system dynamics analysis of intensive pig farming eco-energy system based on the rate variable fundamental in-tree model", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Joglekar, Nitin with Paulo Figueiredo, "Dynamics of Project Screening in a Product Development Pipeline", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - John, Klaus, "The Economics of Biomass-to-Liquids Fuels", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Jones, Charles, "Mental Models in an Emerging Industry: The Photovoltaic Industry in Massachusetts", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Juerging, Jan, "Engineering Change Orders influencing manufacturing start-ups", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Kampmann, Christian Erik with Rogelio Oliva, "Analytical methods for structural dominance analysis in system dynamics: An assessment of the current state of affairs", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Kapmeier, Florian with Martin Schmalz and Theodor Ackbarow, "Happiness - Cracking the Equilibrium State of People's Well-Being", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Katsamakas, Evangelos with Nicholas Georgantzas, "Open source software development: A systems dynamics model", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Kelic, Andjelka with Elissa Matthews and Walt Beyeler, "Telecommunications Operations Resiliency: Labor Shortages and the Voice Network", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Kennedy, Michael with Carol Frances, "The current activities and plans of the SDS Education SIG", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Kim, Hyun-Shil with Namsung Ahn, Jaekook Yu and Yong-Beum Yoon, "The Effects of the New Capacity Investment Behavior in the Korea Wholesale Electricity Market", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Kim, Hyunjung, "In Search of a Mental-Model-Like Concept for Group Level Modeling", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Kim, Sang-Joon, "When Cognitive Institution Collapses: A Case of "Master Kim" through a System Dynamics Model on the Action-Driven Process", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Kljajic Borstnar, Mirjana with Miroljub Kljajic, Andrej Skraba and Davorin Kofjac, "A Model of Group Learning Supported by Simulation Experiment", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Koblov, Andrey with Vladimir Shiryaev, "Firm Behavior Optimal Control on Mobile Service Market", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Kossik, Rick, "Getting Started with GoldSim Software", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Kulhavy, Rudolf, "Bayesian Analysis of Stochastic System Dynamics", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Kunc, Martin, "To Cluster or Not to Cluster: A Simulation Study of Managerial Practices for Innovating in SMEs", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2
      - Laidler-Kylander, Nathalie with Bernard Simonin, "Modeling Brand Equity in International Nonprofit Organizations: A System Dynamics Approach", 2007 July 29-2007 August 2